forwpblogger.com 2015-03-14

# Privacy Policy - forwpblogger

### Privacy Policy

 **forwpblogger respects your privacy.**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of forwpblogger.

For newsletter management and distribution forwpblogger uses services offered by [Mailchimp](http://mailchimp.com/ "mailchimp") and [Google’s Feedburner](http://feedburner.google.com/). While these are established companies that are known to be reliable when it comes to keeping their servers secure we can’t be held responsible/liable for any breaches or customer data loss that may occur at those companies.

 **Credit card details**

forwpblogger will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on forwpblogger.

 **External Sites.**

forwpblogger is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the [privacy policy](http://forwpblogger.com/privacy-policy/) of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

 **Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows forwpblogger to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and forwpblogger does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

 **Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to forwpblogger and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through forwpblogger have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information email [webmaster](mailto:admin@forwpblogger.com)
